[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the US, Medicare Part B is primarily coverage for which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Non-hospital services", "incorrect_answers": ["Hospital admissions", "Medications", "Dialysis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Joe Dirt, who is Joe Dirt talking to when he relates his life story?", "correct_answer": "a radio station D.J.", "incorrect_answers": ["a TV newsman", "a public official", "patrons of a diner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Schiphol Airport is the main airport of this city.", "correct_answer": "Amsterdam", "incorrect_answers": ["Brussels", "Berlin", "Vienna"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1983 movie, starring Robert Duvall, was about a recovering alcoholic country singer who reaches out to a widow and her son and manages to turn his life around?", "correct_answer": "Tender Mercies", "incorrect_answers": ["Terms of Endearment", "Ghostbusters", "Ordinary People"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jupiters magnetic field is the strongest in the Solar System.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are only 10 weight classes in male professional boxing.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call an angle of less than 90 degrees?", "correct_answer": "acute", "incorrect_answers": ["reflex", "oblique", "obtuse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of animals does the G-force team primarily consist of?", "correct_answer": "Guinea pigs", "incorrect_answers": ["Moles", "Rats", "Hamsters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first version of Microsoft Windows to support Plug and Play?", "correct_answer": "Windows 95", "incorrect_answers": ["Windows 3.11", "Windows XP", "Windows 3.0"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The state with the largest area in the lower 48 is?", "correct_answer": "Texas", "incorrect_answers": ["California", "Montana", "Arizona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Identify the property used in this addition equation: 678 + 45 = 45 + 678.", "correct_answer": "Commutative property", "incorrect_answers": ["Associative property", "Distributive property", "Identity property"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the county jail seen in the opening credits of the movie The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "Clatsop County Jail", "incorrect_answers": ["Stoclap County Jail", "Ecola County Jail", "Cannon County Jail"]}]